wpxhosting.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy - WPX Hosting

**K Media Tech Ltd** ("us", "we", "our") operates **WPX Hosting** (the "Site(s)" or "website(s)") and regards our customers' (the "user", "you", "your") privacy with utmost respect and importance.

Information that we collect from you and that you provide to us enables WPX Hosting to inform you about products and services that you have registered an interest in.

Furthermore, by providing us with your information, you consent to us processing it for the purpose outlined above. **Don't worry, we will not pass on your information to any third party**.

By visiting our website, you therefore accept and consent to the practices described in this policy.

For the purposes of **GDPR** , the 'Data Controller' is **K Мedia Tech Ltd** (owners of WPX Hosting).

### So, what sort of information do you collect?

**Personal Information:** When you register to use our website, sign up for any regular newsletter, information services, web forum or consultancy, place an order on our site and/or when you report a problem with our site or otherwise contact us, you provide information that we may record.

**_Note_ :** _Information that we collect may include your name, address, email address and phone number, as well as relevant financial and credit card information._

**Inquiries:** By _completing forms_ on our website, or by _corresponding_ with us via telephone, email, Live Chat, or Facebook (etc.), we may collect this information too.

**Log Data:** As is typical for many site operators, we collect information sent by your browser whenever you visit our site.

This _Log Data_ may include technical details such as: your IP address, login information, your browser type, version, and its plugins, as well as your time zone, operating system, and platform.

We may also collect information about your visit, such as: the full URL clickstream to, through, and from our site (including the date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visit, page interaction details, methods used to browse away from the page; if you were linked to our site from another website and its address, as well as the address of the search engine that may have brought you to our site.

**External Data:** We may receive information about you if you use any other website or service we operate.

We also work closely with third parties (e.g: business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies, etc.) and may receive information about you from them.

### OK, but what do you DO with this information?

Because your personal information is so valuable to both you and us, we strongly believe in minimising the personal information we collect as well as limiting its use and purpose.

We will use this information as necessary to carry out our obligations, arising from any contracts between you and us, for which we have been given permission.

This information may also be used as required or permitted for legal compliance or other lawful purposes, as well as to provide you with the products and services you request from us and notify you about any changes in that regard.

### In technical terms, your information is primarily used to:

  * Improve internal operations, such as troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, and for statistical and survey purposes;

  * Improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

  * Allow you to participate in interactive features of our services, when you choose to do so;

  * Maintain our site safety and security;

  * Measure and understand the effectiveness of advertising intended for you and others, and therefore to deliver relevant advertising to you;

  * Offer suggestions and recommendations to you and other users regarding our products or services that may be of interest.

We may combine these details with information we have already collected from you as well as what you have already provided.

### Do you share this information?

**No, your information is not transferred in connection with the operation of our business, including to our related companies.**

Your personal data shall not be processed by these companies and/or by our and their respective employees and service providers.

By submitting personal data, you agree that only we shall store and process it.

Where permitted by law, we reserve the right to release personal data without your consent and/or without consulting you, when we believe that this is appropriate to comply with our legal obligations, to protect the security of our website and related technologies, to prevent and minimise the effects of fraud, and otherwise to protect our legitimate interests and/or the legitimate interests of our customers.

### How do you store my information?

As standard, we may store your information in hard copy or electronic format within storage facilities which we own and operate ourselves, or that are owned and operated by our service providers.

It is possible that some of your information that we hold may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the **European Economic Area** ('EEA') which may not provide the same level of protection as within the **EEA**. It may also be processed by personnel operating outside the EEA who work for us, one of our service providers, or another entitiy.

**Any such transfers of personal data outside the EEA will comply with the requirements of the GDPR**.

By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing, and/or processing.

We retain your personal data for so long as is necessary with regard to the purposes for which it was collected or lawfully processed further, or for so long as may be necessary in light of our legal obligations.

### Is my information safe?

All reasonably necessary steps will be taken to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We seek to ensure that we keep your personal data accurate and up to date however, **you are responsible for informing us of any changes to your personal data** and other information (such as a change in contact details).

While we take these steps to maintain the security of your information, you should be aware of the many information security risks that exist and take appropriate care to help safeguard your information.

The nature of the Internet is such that we cannot guarantee the security of the information you transmit to us electronically, and any transmission is done at your own risk.

We store information that you provide to us on secure servers and deploy appropriate technical and organisational security measures in the storage and disclosure of your personal data to prevent unauthorised access or loss.

**_Note_ :** _You may revoke your consent to the processing of your data at any time by sending an email to[support@wpxhosting.com](mailto:support@wpxhosting.com)_

If you would like information about any personal data we hold about you, or would like to correct or delete that information, you may contact us at any time.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.

Please check their policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.

Please check back frequently for any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy.

As WPX Hosting is not a hosting reseller, WPX Hosting customers do not need a DPA (Data Protection Agreement) with us to comply with GDPR regulations.

### RESOURCES
